class Flashcard {
  final String question;
  final String answer;

  Flashcard({required this.question, required this.answer});
}
//Questions
List<Flashcard> quesAnsList = [
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q1. Why Did You Decide to Become a Software Engineer?",
      answer: "I decided to become software engineer because I love to solve problems by programming them."),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q2.What programming languages do you prefer?",
      answer: "I prefer to program in either Python, Java, or C++ because it allows me to have a variety of languages for different purposes. "),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q3.What’s important when checking a team member’s code?",
      answer: "I want to be checking if their code is efficient and simplistic. "),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q4.What project management tools have you used?",
      answer: "I've used tools such as microsoft office, flowcharts, and Jira ."),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q5.Talk about a project you completed successfully?" ,
      answer: "One of the Projects I have completed successfully is a comparison of matrix multiplication using three different algorithms."
          "I used classical, strassen and divide and conquer algorithm. "),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q6. What Are You Looking for in This Job?",
      answer: "I am looking for a job that will challenge me and somewhere I can make my team and company better."),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q7.Why Should We Hire You",
      answer: "You should hire me because I have proven to work under pressure and from my personal experience I have as a software engineer. "),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q8.Talk about some mistakes you learned from?",
      answer: "Some mistakes I have learned from in the past is procrastinating and being the last one on my team to get work done. "),
  Flashcard(
      question: "Q9.What is object-oriented programming?",
      answer: "bject-oriented programming (OOP) is a computer programming model that organizes software design around data,"
          " or objects, rather than functions and logic. "),
  Flashcard(
      question: "",
      answer: ""),

];